[
    [
        "Kenyan Firms Eye Deals During Obama Summit Tagged : The Global Entrepreneurship Summit , launched by President Obama in 2009 , brings together entrepreneurs and investors from across Africa and around the world annually to showcase innovative projects , exchange new ideas , and help spur economic opportunity .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    30,
                    35,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    111,
                    116,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    183,
                    189,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "By Neville Otuki Kenya \"s\" business leaders were Monday planning how best to exploit the deal - making opportunities in the country \"s\" history starting this Friday when the world convenes in Nairobi for the Global Entrepreneurship Summit ( GES ) .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    3,
                    16,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    17,
                    22,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    192,
                    199,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Industrialists , entrepreneurs and bankers said through their unions , they were keen to find global partners with expertise and financial clout to help drive their expansion in East Africa and beyond .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    178,
                    189,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "More on This Kenya : Mombasa Road , Uhuru Highway , Waiyaki Way Among Roads to Be Closed During Obama Visit - Police Expansion of the private sector - the engine of the economy - would trigger economic activity , ignite productivity and create the much needed jobs for the millions of unemployed youth .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    13,
                    18,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    21,
                    33,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    36,
                    49,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    52,
                    75,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    96,
                    101,
                    "PER"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "\" Local manufacturers will be looking for joint venture deals and partnerships to boost their capacity for growth through skills transfer besides new capital injection , \" the Kenya Association of Manufacturers ( KAM ) CEO Phyllis Wakiaga said .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    176,
                    210,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    213,
                    216,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    223,
                    238,
                    "PER"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "A number of industrialists have opened talks with their global counterparts who have arrived in Kenya ahead of the GES which opens in Nairobi on July 24 and will be attended by US President Barack Obama .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    96,
                    101,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    134,
                    141,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    177,
                    179,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    190,
                    202,
                    "PER"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The manufacturers , like other local entrepreneurs and innovators , have been allocated exhibition stands at the summit venue from where they will showcase their products and facilitate investors interested in entering East Africa \"s\" largest economy .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    219,
                    230,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Kenya Bankers Association chief executive Habil Olaka said lenders would be keen to find financing opportunities in deals struck between local and foreign entrepreneurs for new and established ventures .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    25,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    42,
                    53,
                    "PER"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "\" The summit will provide lenders with a platform to showcase their products , \" said Mr Olaka adding that Nairobi \"s\" hosting of the global event was a vote of confidence in the economy .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    89,
                    94,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    107,
                    114,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Kenya accounted for the lion \"s\" share of private equity in East Africa taking 63 per cent of the reported $ 800 million worth of deals between 2007 and 2014 .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    5,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    60,
                    71,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The private equity survey by financial consultancy KPMG and the East Africa Venture Capital Association ( Eavca ) released last month placed Kenya ahead of ahead of Ethiopia , Tanzania , Rwanda and Uganda .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    51,
                    55,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    64,
                    103,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    106,
                    111,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    141,
                    146,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    165,
                    173,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    176,
                    184,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    187,
                    193,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    198,
                    204,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Several state - backed agencies charged with promoting and attracting foreign direct investments will also be on a charm offensive to sell the country .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "The list includes Kenya Investment Authority , Kenya National Chamber of Commerce & Industry and the Brand Kenya Board .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    18,
                    44,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    47,
                    92,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    101,
                    118,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Kenya is the first country in sub - Saharan Africa to host the annual summit and second in Africa after last year \"s\" edition in Morocco .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    5,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    30,
                    50,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    91,
                    97,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    129,
                    136,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "President Uhuru Kenyatta is co-hosting the summit with his American counterpart .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    10,
                    24,
                    "PER"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Kenya \"s\" private sector last year lost its jobs creation momentum in the wake of a slow - down in growth to 5.3 per cent from 5.7 per cent the previous year .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    5,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Official data shows that the sector created 69,600 formal jobs down from 106,200 the previous year .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "In comparison , the public sector created a paltry 17,500 jobs last year , underlining the critical role of the private sector in jobs growth .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Launched by President Obama in 2009 , GES brings together entrepreneurs and investors from across Africa and around the world annually to showcase innovative projects , exchange new ideas , and help spur economic opportunity .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    22,
                    27,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    38,
                    41,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    98,
                    104,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The 2015 GES agenda will focus on generating new investments for entrepreneurs , with a particular focus on women and youth .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    9,
                    12,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Billionaire businessman Chris Kirubi said that he expected the summit to translate into increased dealings between Kenya and the US and capital inflows .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    24,
                    36,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    115,
                    120,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    129,
                    131,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "KAM said the recent renewal of the African Growth and Opportunity Act ( Agoa ) , which allows exports to the US duty free , would help balance Kenya \"s\" global trade .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    3,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    109,
                    111,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    143,
                    148,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "\" We have in the past not utilised the Agoa opportunity to its full potential .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "We have only been strong on the textile front .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "It \"s\" high time we leveraged on the remaining 6400 products that enjoy tax - free access to the US market , \" said Ms Wakiaga adding that Kenya needs to invest in value addition to sharpen its competitiveness even in the absence of such preference treatment .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    97,
                    99,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    119,
                    126,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    139,
                    144,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Kenya \"s\" exports to the US stood at Ksh38 billion , attributable largely to the Agoa trade agreement , which was recently renewed for another 10 years .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    5,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    25,
                    27,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The Agoa window , introduced by former President Bill Clinton \"s\" administration in 2000 , allows Kenya and other African countries to export more than 6,000 goods to the US without paying taxes .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    49,
                    61,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    98,
                    103,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    171,
                    173,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Last year , Kenya for first time bought more goods from the United States than it did from the whole of Africa , underlining growing commercial ties that are expected to deepen with the entrepreneurship summit .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    12,
                    17,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    60,
                    73,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    104,
                    110,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "US exports to Kenya rose to Ksh168 billion last year compared to the Ksh146 billion worth of goods and services that came from Africa , according to data from the Kenya National Bureau of Statistics ( KNBS ) .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    2,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    14,
                    19,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    127,
                    133,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    163,
                    198,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    201,
                    205,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "This made America Kenya \"s\" third largest source of its imports , behind China and India .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    10,
                    23,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    73,
                    78,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    83,
                    88,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "\" Direct flights to the US will also help increase activity between the two countries , \" said Ms Wakiaga .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    24,
                    26,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    98,
                    105,
                    "PER"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "More on This",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "China market rout , slowing economy sap demand for luxury cars Reuters – 23 minutes ago Change By Norihiko Shirouzu BEIJING ( Reuters ) - Prices for German luxury cars in China are tumbling as the country \"s\" stock market sell - off and worries about broader economic growth chill demand for auto brands that once commanded price premiums from affluent Chinese consumers .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    5,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    63,
                    70,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    98,
                    115,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    116,
                    123,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    126,
                    133,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    171,
                    176,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "At Mercedes - Benz stores operated by a dealer group with nearly 200 multiple brand outlets , customer traffic at showrooms has dwindled markedly since mid-June , when a stock market slide that saw indexes plunge by as much as a third began .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    3,
                    18,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "A senior manager at that dealer chain said customer traffic at some of its Mercedes - Benz stores was \" down 20 percent to 30 percent \" compared with last year \"s\" levels over the past month .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    75,
                    90,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Dealing with a similar fall - off in customer traffic and orders , a dozen BMW stores run by another dealer group are being forced to provide increasingly steep discounts to entice customers , according to the head of the chain with showrooms across China .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    75,
                    78,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    250,
                    255,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "He said business had already been weak , due to China \"s\" slowing economic growth and a corruption crackdown that has weighed on sales of flashy cars , and his stores had to offer a 5 percent discount to grease sales last year .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    48,
                    53,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Over the last week or two , as the stock market rout pummelled the net worth of potential buyers , many of those stores were forced to offer steeper discounts on cars such as the BMW X6 crossover SUV , according to the dealer group chief .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "\" The business has been slow for the last 18 months , but lately we have had to discount even more , \" the dealer operator said , asking for anonymity because he did not want to damage his group \"s\" relationship with BMW .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    217,
                    220,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "\" When people walk into a showroom now , with anything less than 15 percent discount they would not even consider opening their wallets . \"",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Jimmy Cao , a Beijing - based BMW spokesman , said he was not able to provide an immediate comment .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    9,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    14,
                    21,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    30,
                    33,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The average \" maker suggested retail price \" ( MSRP ) for all passenger cars remains relatively high in China , at around 280,000 yuan ( $ 45,000 ) , according to research firm JATO Dynamics .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    104,
                    109,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    177,
                    190,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "But actual prices customers pay when buying cars have fallen steadily since 2012 to slightly less than 170,000 yuan , chiefly because of heavy discounting by dealers , according to JATO .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    181,
                    185,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "SALES FORECAST CUT",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "In the first sign that turmoil in the stock market could affect spending in the real economy , China \"s\" automakers \"\" association on Friday slashed its 2015 forecast for vehicle sales growth to a meagre 3 percent .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    95,
                    100,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The China Association of Automobile Manufacturers ( CAAM ) previously predicted combined sales for passenger and commercial vehicles to grow 7 percent to 25.1 million this year .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    4,
                    49,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    52,
                    56,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "\" The stock market has some impact on the car sales as it hurts cash flow , \" CAAM chief Dong Yang told reporters on Friday , adding he was confident sales would pick up in the second half .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    78,
                    82,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    89,
                    98,
                    "PER"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Defending the double - digit operating margins that the China car market provided just a few years ago is not easy as the economy cools to its slowest pace in growth in a quarter century , and auto dealers in China are tightening their belts to keep margins from falling further .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    56,
                    61,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    209,
                    214,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The BMW dealer group chief said his outlets , which employ about 200 people at each location , had put a hold on new hires .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    4,
                    7,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "\" We have not instituted pay cuts , but we have actually frozen salary increases as well , \" he said .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "The dealer group chief was also trying to persuade the German brand to lower the bar for bonuses and rebates – a primary source of profitability for most dealers – by reducing its sales volume objectives for his stores .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "\" If the factory actually lowered our targets , we would \"nt\" have so much pressure to discount in trying to achieve our targets , \" he said .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Several automakers , including General Motors Co and Volkswagen AG , have already readjusted their pricing strategies in China by pushing down MSRPs closer to prevailing transaction levels .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    31,
                    48,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    53,
                    66,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    121,
                    126,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "GM \"s\" Shanghai - based spokeswoman Irene Shen said by email the Detroit automaker was not considering lay - offs or big productions cuts .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    2,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    7,
                    15,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    36,
                    46,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    65,
                    72,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "\" GM is committed to China and intends to continue to grow and enhance our business working with our partners in China , \" she said .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    2,
                    4,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    21,
                    26,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    113,
                    118,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "\" We have made no major moves to curtail production .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "We regularly manage our production volumes to maintain inventories within a healthy range . \"",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Global automakers would , in any case , find it hard to make significant lay - offs in China , given they are mostly partnered with Chinese state - owned car makers who defer to Beijing \"s\" priority of defending social stability by safeguarding jobs .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    87,
                    92,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    178,
                    185,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "\" For high profile JVs , it would be difficult to make more radical restructuring moves like larger scale lay - offs and capacity reductions , \" James Chao , Shanghai - based Asia -Pacific managing director at industry consultant IHS Automotive .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    145,
                    155,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    158,
                    166,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    175,
                    188,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    230,
                    244,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "( $ 1 = 6.2092 Chinese yuan renminbi ) ( Editing by Alex Richardson )",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    52,
                    67,
                    "PER"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Other Articles Split child - care duties for a \"\" super \"\" sex life !",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Spiritual awareness varies throughout the day : Study Selfies can give clues to your personality",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "The hippocampus in the brain ’s temporal lobe is not only responsible for long - term memory , but also involved in quick and successful conflict resolution , researchers have found .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "In their everyday life , people are constantly confronted with decision conflicts , especially if they need to suppress an action that would have made sense under normal circumstances .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "For example : when the pedestrian lights go green , a pedestrian would normally start walking .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "If , however , a car comes speeding along at the same time , the pedestrian should stay where he is .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "In their experiment , researchers headed by Dr Nikolai Axmacher from the Ruhr - Universitat Bochum ( RUB ) in Germany , together with colleagues from the University Hospital of Bonn as well as in Aachen and Birmingham opted for a less threatening situation .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    47,
                    63,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    73,
                    98,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    101,
                    104,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    110,
                    117,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    154,
                    181,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    196,
                    202,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    207,
                    217,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Test participants heard the words “ high ” or “ low ” spoken in a high or low tone , and they had to state – regardless of the meaning of the word – at what pitch the speaker said them .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "If the pitch does n’t correspond with the meaning of the word , a conflict is generated : the participants would answer more slowly and make more mistakes .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "The team demonstrated with two different measurement methods that the hippocampus is active in such conflicting situations ; this applies particularly when a person solves the conflicts quickly and successfully .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Axmacher and colleagues analysed the brain activity in healthy participants with functional magnetic resonance imaging .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    8,
                    "PER"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "They gained the same results in epilepsy patients who had EEG electrodes implanted in the hippocampus for the purpose of surgery planning ; this is how the researchers could measure the activity in that brain region directly .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Because the hippocampus is essential for memory , the researchers speculate about its role in conflict resolution .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "“ Our data show first of all a completely new function of the Hippocampus – processing of activity conflicts , ” said Carina Oehrn from the Department of Epileptology at the University Hospital of Bonn .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    118,
                    130,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    140,
                    166,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    174,
                    201,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "“ However , in order to answer the question how that function interacts with memory processes , we will have to carry out additional tests , ” said Oehrn .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    148,
                    153,
                    "PER"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "“ Perhaps the memory system becomes particularly active if a conflict has been successfully resolved , ” said Axmacher .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    110,
                    118,
                    "PER"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The study was published in the journal Current Biology .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    39,
                    54,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "22 , 2015 9:57 am",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "361 Capital Soft Closes the 361 Managed Futures Strategy Fund September 10 , 2015 08:00 ET | Source : 361 Capital LLC DENVER , Sept. 10 , 361 Capital , a leading boutique asset manager offering institutional - quality alternative mutual funds , today announced the soft close of the 361 Capital Managed Futures Strategy Fund , a fund which employs a distinct counter - trend approach in the pursuit of attractive risk - adjusted returns that exhibit low correlations to traditional stock and bond investments .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    11,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    118,
                    124,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    138,
                    149,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The fund will be closed to new investors beginning September 30 , 2015 .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "\" With that in mind , we \"ve\" put forth great effort into measuring the capacity of our strategies , in order to ensure that asset growth does \"nt\" degrade return potential . \"",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "With AUM just over $ 1 billion as of September 8 , the fund will be closing to new investors but will still allow additional capacity for current investors .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    5,
                    8,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The executives and investment team at 361 Capital understand that when firms lose sight of performance objectives and chase assets under management , investors ultimately pay the price .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    38,
                    49,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "\" We are grateful to our clients and investors who have helped us achieve this accomplishment and thankful for their investment in our philosophy , people and strategy , \" said Florence .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    177,
                    185,
                    "PER"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "For more information about the 361 Managed Futures Strategy Fund closing or questions about implementing alternative investment products , contact 866-361-1720 .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "About 361 Capital 361 Capital is a leading boutique asset manager offering institutional - quality alternative mutual funds to investment advisors and their clients .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    6,
                    29,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Since its founding in 2001 , the firm has focused exclusively on alternative investments , creating innovative portfolio solutions that seek to help advisors better understand and manage portfolio risk .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Today , the firm combines its investment skills , experience and focus on transparency with that of other world - class investment managers to offer a family of single - manager alternative mutual funds , including managed futures , global counter - trend , long / short equity , and macro mutual funds .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "For more information , call 866-361-1720 or visit www.361capital.com .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Investors should consider the 361 Funds \"\" investment objectives , risks , charges and expenses carefully before investing .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "For a prospectus , or summary prospectus , that contains this and other information about the Funds , call 1-888-736-1227 or visit www.361capital.com .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Please read the prospectus or summary prospectus carefully before investing .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Past performance does not guarantee future results .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Futures prices can be very volatile .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Leverage ( the small margin required for futures contracts ) means that a relatively small market movement can have a disproportionately large effect on the Fund \"s\" investments .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Leverage can result in large losses as well as gains .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "The potential loss from a contract could exceed the Fund \"s\" initial investment .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "With short contracts , the loss is theoretically unlimited since the appreciation of the underlying asset also is theoretically unlimited .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Fund assets not invested in futures are invested primarily in investment - grade debt .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "The value of debt instruments generally falls when interest rates rise .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "The Fund may engage in frequent trading , the costs of which may reduce returns and result in a greater number of taxable transactions .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "The Fund may invest a large portion of its assets in relatively few issuers , potentially making it more volatile than a diversified fund .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "The 361 Funds are distributed by IMST Distributors , LLC .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    33,
                    56,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Related Articles",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "EXCLUSIVE Steve Harker , The Australian Financial Markets Association \"s\" new chairman .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    10,
                    22,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    29,
                    69,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Photo : Michel \"OSullivan\"",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    8,
                    26,
                    "PER"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The Australian Financial Markets Association has elected Morgan Stanley \"s\" Steve Harker as its new chairman , as it works towards releasing a revamped code of conduct for its members within the next three months .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    4,
                    44,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    57,
                    71,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    76,
                    88,
                    "PER"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Mr Harker , Morgan Stanley \"s\" local chief , replaces Stephen Roberts at the helm of AFMA .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    3,
                    9,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    12,
                    26,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    54,
                    69,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    85,
                    89,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Mr Roberts stepped down following his transition to chairman of Citigroup Australia from the chief executive role .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    3,
                    10,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    64,
                    83,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The industry is being very proactive in dealing with these issues .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Steve Harker , Morgan Stanley",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    12,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    15,
                    29,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The changeover comes as the industry has continued to be marred by probes involving potential manipulation of the bank bill swap rate and incidents of questionable practices in the provision of financial advice .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Mr Harker outlined the increased importance of improving behaviour and culture and consulting effectively on public policy , including tax and regulatory matters , as the finance industry continued to navigate the fallout from the global financial crisis .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    3,
                    9,
                    "PER"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Advertisement \" It \"s\" important the industry as a whole signs up to it [ new code of conduct and ethics ] because you always risk having some marginal individuals who give the industry a bad name , \" he told Fairfax Media .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    209,
                    222,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "\" The industry is being very proactive in dealing with these issues … the bar continues to be raised and I think that \"s\" appropriate , \" Mr Harker added , noting that industry bodies and companies were working toward improving culture , and raising standards and education levels of those working in financial markets .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    141,
                    147,
                    "PER"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "AFMA \"s\" chief David Lynch said the association was working with members to revise its code of conduct and ethics , providing a more comprehensive document that will beef up stipulations around ethical principles .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    4,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    15,
                    26,
                    "PER"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "That last document was dated January 2011 , but AFMA also periodically releases guidance notes on topics including debt trading and confidential information and the conduct of market soundings .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    48,
                    52,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The new AFMA document will also draw on the United Kingdom \"s\" Fair and Effective Markets Review , which was partly established to restore trust in financial markets .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    8,
                    12,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    44,
                    58,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Commonwealth Bank of Australia \"s\" Kelly Bayer Rosmarin\​ was elected AFMA \"s\" deputy chair , following the departure of former Westpac Banking Corp executive Rob Whitfield .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    30,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    35,
                    61,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    74,
                    78,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    132,
                    152,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    163,
                    176,
                    "PER"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Ms Bayer Rosmarin is CBA \"s\" group executive for institutional banking and markets .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    3,
                    17,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    21,
                    24,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Hr Harker is also on the Future Fund Board of Guardians and was this year \"s\" joint inductee into the stockbroker \"s\" hall of fame .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    3,
                    9,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    25,
                    55,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "AFMA is also busy on a raft of regulatory , tax and policy issues , and is keenly awaiting the federal government \"s\" response to the landmark financial system inquiry .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    4,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Among other things , AFMA \"s\" submissions to the FSI highlighted the need for taxation matters to be considered due to their influence on financial markets , and underscored the importance of the local corporate bond market .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    21,
                    25,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    49,
                    52,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Earlier this month , AFMA said it supported the corporate regulator \"s\" recommendations on the administration of financial benchmarks in Australia .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    21,
                    25,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    137,
                    146,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "It is also liaising with an Australian Securities Exchange working group on a simultaneous move to a shorter two - day settlement cycle for debt and equities markets .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    28,
                    58,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "AFMA represents more than 130 members , such as local and international banks , brokers , securities companies , state government treasury corporations , fund managers , and traders in electricity and other specialised markets .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    4,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Chris Bowen has said that the effects test could lead to some large legal bills .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    11,
                    "PER"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Andrew Meares Share on twitter Share on Google Plus by Primrose Riordan Shadow Treasurer Chris Bowen has warned small and medium businesses advocating the effects test to brace for \" a conga line \" of lawyers and bills if it goes through Parliament .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    13,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    23,
                    30,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    40,
                    51,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    55,
                    78,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    89,
                    100,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    238,
                    248,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The Coalition is considering introducing the effects test , a controversial recommendation of the Harper review , which would change section 46 of the Competition",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    4,
                    13,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    98,
                    104,
                    "PER"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Act so it only has to be shown that the effect , not the purpose , of a decision would be to eliminate competition .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Addressing a high - level grocers meet in Canberra on Wednesday , Mr Bowen said it was a \" dangerous \" move that would result in a \" lawyers picnic \" for small business .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    42,
                    50,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    69,
                    74,
                    "PER"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Effects test \" If an effects test were to be introduced , and you were unable to convince the Australian Competition and Consumer Commission to take your case , be prepared to be facing a conga line of silks and consultants , with a potential legal bill that could be multiples of a small firms \"\" turnover , \" he said .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    94,
                    140,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "\" There is a risk of significant adverse cost orders should an applicant lose when trying to take action under an \"\" effects test \"\" . \"",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "He acknowledged a number of the grocers in the room held a different view on the effects test , and believe it will help regulate the power of large supermarkets .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "A broad group , including t he Australian Chamber of Commerce and Industry , Master Grocers Australia , the Australian Hotels Association , the Australian Retailers Association and the National Farmers Federation , are pushing for the test .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    31,
                    74,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    77,
                    101,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    108,
                    137,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    144,
                    176,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    185,
                    212,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Master Grocers Australia CEO",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    24,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Jos de Bruin slammed Mr Bowen \"s\" comments , suggesting he was being fed by the big business lobby .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    12,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    24,
                    29,
                    "PER"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "\" There is absolutely no substance to what he was saying … all that was , was a scare campaign , \" he said .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Australian Chamber of Commerce and Industry chief executive Kate Carnell has also backed the effects test , saying it was a reasonable compromise that would not stymie competition nor hike prices to rise .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    43,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    60,
                    72,
                    "PER"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The current test only requires proof of an anti-competitive purpose or intent , which advocates argue has led to practically no successful prosecutions under the law .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Mr Bowen also said Labor was against extending the base of the GST to food , as it could feed Australia \"s\" diabetes epidemic .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    3,
                    8,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    19,
                    24,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    94,
                    103,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        ".",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "View photo A customer shops at a Wal - Mart store in Beijing , February 18 , 2014 .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    33,
                    43,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    53,
                    60,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "REUTERS / Kim Kyung - Hoon SHANGHAI ( Reuters ) - A unit of conglomerate China Resources Corp plans to sell minority stakes it holds in 21 Wal - Mart Stores Inc ( WMT .N ) outlets around China , a spokesman for the U.S . retailer told Reuters on Friday .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    7,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    10,
                    26,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    27,
                    35,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    38,
                    45,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    73,
                    93,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    139,
                    160,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    163,
                    169,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    187,
                    192,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    215,
                    220,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    235,
                    242,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "State - backed China Resources SZITIC",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    15,
                    37,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Trust Co Ltd has listed its stakes in the stores as being for sale for a combined 3.3 billion yuan ( $ 525 million ) , according to official postings from the firm on the Shanghai United Assets and Equity Exchange .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    12,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    171,
                    213,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The postings did \"nt\" make clear the reason for selling the stakes - almost all of which account for 35 percent of the jointly owned outlets - and China Resources did not respond to phone calls and emailed requests seeking comment .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    147,
                    162,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The sale comes as Wal - Mart , the world \"s\" largest retailer , and other largely brick and mortar retailers face intense competition in China from fast - developing online rivals just as growth in the world \"s\" second - largest economy cools .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    18,
                    28,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    137,
                    142,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Wal - Mart , France \"s\" Carrefour SA ( CARR",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    10,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    13,
                    19,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    24,
                    36,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    39,
                    43,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        ".PA ) and Britain \"s\" Tesco PLC ( TSCO.L ) have all seen sales growth slip over the last five years in China , losing market share to local rivals , according to consumer analytics firm Kantar Worldpanel .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    3,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    10,
                    17,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    22,
                    31,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    34,
                    40,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    103,
                    108,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    186,
                    203,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "A China - based spokesman for Wal - Mart said the firm respected the \" investment decision \" of its partner , adding the sale should not impact the retailer \"s\" ongoing business in the market .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    2,
                    7,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    30,
                    40,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "\" Wal - Mart believes that the transfer of minority interest will not influence Wal - Mart \"s\" operation and development in China , \" spokesman David Fu said in emailed comments to Reuters .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    2,
                    12,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    80,
                    90,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    124,
                    129,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    144,
                    152,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    181,
                    188,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Fu did \"nt\" comment on who might potentially buy the stakes up for sale .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    2,
                    "PER"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The notices , dated last week but carried by domestic media earlier on Friday , listed the stakes for sale at prices ranging from as little as 1 yuan and up to 2.6 billion yuan .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "The stores were located from China \"s\" western Sichuan province to Beijing .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    29,
                    34,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    47,
                    54,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    67,
                    74,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Wal - Mart has been trying to boost its online presence in China and reduce reliance on physical stores .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    10,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    59,
                    64,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The retailer took full ownership of local e-commerce firm Yihaodian.com in July , buying the 49 percent stake it did not already own .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    58,
                    71,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The U.S . retailer has been struggling to shore up its profit margins globally , which have been weighed down by a $ 1 billion investment announced earlier this year to increase wages for half a million store - level workers , along with other cost pressures .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    4,
                    9,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The company \"s\" stock is down around 22 percent so far this year .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "( $ 1 = 6.3484 Chinese yuan renminbi )",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "( Reporting by Adam Jourdan and SHANGHAI Newsroom ; Editing by Kazunori Takada and Kenneth Maxwell ) Wal - Mart Stores Inc China Resources",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    15,
                    27,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    32,
                    49,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    63,
                    78,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    83,
                    98,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    101,
                    138,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Bank accounts",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Which bank should I switch to ?",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "We highlight our five favourite bank accounts on the market , depending on what you want : customer service , perks , interest , loyalty or cashback A generation ago , the perks of opening a current account was receiving a piggy bank .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Now you can get 5 pc interest or generous cashback By Amelia Murray",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    54,
                    67,
                    "PER"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "( MENAFN Press ) Integratus Solutions is co-presenting their Data Warehouse Success Story with CP Kelco During a Webcast Coming Up August 19 2015",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    2,
                    14,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    17,
                    37,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    95,
                    103,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The company offers pre-built Business Intelligence ( BI ) & Data Warehouse ( DW ) solutions to integrate cloud & on - premise data enabling self - service reporting for executives department heads managers & administrators .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "This interview is free to re-publish .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Ron what are some of the top issues you hear when talking to CIO’s ?",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    3,
                    "PER"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Without a doubt the number one issue we consistently hear from CIO ’s across the board is how to get information out to the enterprise into the hands of the people who need it to do their jobs on a day to day basis .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "All organizations have invested significant amounts of money in many cases anywhere from hundreds of millions to billions of dollars into their transactional systems to improve efficiency manage their business and capture valuable data on their customers patients financials employees inventory levels and so on .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Often the first challenge is to ensure employees are adopting and using these systems to consistently & accurately capture the data needed for analytics .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Once these systems are in place typically for one or two years organizations realize that an enterprise data warehouse platform is required in order to fully realize the value of their disparate internal and external data .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "As a result - many organizations are investing as much as a 100 million into their data warehouse platform in order to fully realize the value of these investments and achieve competitive advantages whether in operational efficiency cost reduction or finding new revenue opportunities through new product offerings academic research business analysis patient care or other valuable ways to leverage their existing data .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Across all industries we consistently hear that the business is not satisfied with their ability to access actionable data needed to do their job effectively .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "100 million is a lot for a data warehouse how do organizations typically justify the return on this type of investment in their data strategy ?",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "There are three ways to justify spending funds on a data warehouse strategy .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "The first is to reduce the cost of data integration .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "In order to produce a typical enterprise internal or external report it can involve anywhere integrating from 1 to 5 or more data sources .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Locating gathering and merging these disparate data sources typically take 90 % of the time needed to produce a report and can take anywhere from several weeks to months .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "A typical enterprise needs to produce hundreds of reports annually ( for the executives board members regulatory authorities managers etc. ) .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "A typical data integration cost for each report ( locating gathering merging ) can run anywhere from 20000 to 1 or more .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Multiply this number by 100 ( or more ) annual reports and an organizations reporting costs could easily run anywhere from 2M - 10 M / year or higher ( depending on volume and cost per report ) .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "As a result its easy to see how most businesses are not currently satisfied with the quality of reporting they are currently receiving based on the data that ’s available .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "The issue is not with the reporting tools or team however specifically with the lack of a data warehouse strategy & effective implementation .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "An effective data warehouse means the data is located gathered and merged up front enabling the business to write and access their reports directly within the warehouse rather than manually doing this for each and every report request .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "So the first area of cost savings is in the data integration .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "There comes a point when organizations decide do we keep hiring additional people to manually integrate data and write reports or do we implement a data warehouse and allow these people to focus more on analytics instead .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "The second are of value is in data quality .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Its been estimated that poor data quality costs the US economy as much as 3 trillion / year .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    52,
                    54,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "As an example poor data quality results shipments sent to the wrong location and strategic business decisions being made poorly with inaccurate incomplete data .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "How much time is wasted in business meetings debating which department has the accurate sales numbers ?",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "When gathering data on financials employees customers and patients data quality is critical and expensive .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "The third area of value in a data strategy is perhaps the most valuable however very different for each organization .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Business revenue opportunities abound in fully leveraging available data .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Organizations such as Facebook Amazon & Google are leading the world in growth & market capitalization based on business strategies that seek maximize value from their available data .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    22,
                    37,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    40,
                    46,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "As another example I spoke with a BI director from an academic health system who was able to fulfill over 400 research requests as a result of their integrated data warehouse .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "There are countless ways to maximize revenue across all industries by fully leveraging available data on customers and employees .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Organizations who do this will continue to achieve financial stability reduce their risk and achieve high valuations in the future .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "If I ’ve decided to implement a data warehouse strategy what is the best way to reduce overall implementation risk ?",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "As in any endeavor the best way to reduce risk is by relying on professionals with proven experience .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "They will help provide the guidance needed to get through roadblocks and reduce or eliminate potential pitfalls along the way .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "They ’ll help ensure the right resources infrastructure and executive sponsorship is in place to maximize value of your investments .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "The right professional (s ) can help you hire a team of data integration and reporting experts to achieve your initial objectives and continue to evolve your data strategy over time .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "For different organizations this is done in different ratios of internal and external resources but it is always recommended to start with proven experts and check the references of the specific consultant / new hire you ’re bringing on .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Seasoned experts with several successful implementations will be able to provide guidance on getting through roadblocks and avoiding potentially disastrous pitfalls .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "What type of successful data warehouse solutions have you seen organizations implement ?",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Recently we ’ve seen a great deal of organizations moving to cloud applications in order to simplify their IT infrastructure and reduce costs .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Typically these applications satisfy line of business requirements such as HR CRM or other purposes .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Often these applications may be a third party service which provides data on customer and / or patient satisfaction for example .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "In any case integrating data from cloud applications requires additional complexity to ensure this data is effectively included as part of a Data warehouse strategy .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Often this data is hugely valuable containing employee or customer information .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Integrating with financials for example can help provide a complete picture on revenue per employee across location division etc .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "As another example one surgeon may have excellent revenue numbers but perhaps lower patient satisfaction / retention numbers .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Without integrating these data sets there is critical information that goes missing .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "We ’ve recently worked with a large enterprise organization diversified across several businesses from paper to chemical manufacturing among others .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "They recently moved to a cloud HR application called SuccessFactors in order to reduce costs from their previous legacy PeopleSoft application .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "They achieved the initial value desired however wanted to be able to fully leverage this valuable employee data within their robust data warehouse which is supported by the market - share leading Business Objects toolset .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "The data warehouse already was providing valuable insight on their financials inventory and material costs which is captured in their SAP ERP .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Their desire was to correlate this data together with employee costs in order to fully achieve their business objectives .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "They also used ADP for payroll and wanted to incorporate this as well .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "As a result their department heads are able to easily access and forecast data on complex employee compensation scenarios taking into account financial and revenue data .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "There are a great deal of “ prebuilt ” data warehouse and business intelligence applications available in the market for each industry .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Some important questions to ask include the following :",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Is it agnostic to data sources & vendor ?",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "( i.e. if it ’s a vendor data warehouse how difficult is it to integrate data sources outside of that vendor ’s domain of expertise )",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Is it comprehensive for your business requirements ?",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Is it flexible to meet your competitive advantages ?",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "( i.e. if it ’s the same solution your competitors are using ; how do you address the advantages inherent to your organization ? )",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Typically vendor ’s solutions are n’t great at integrating data outside their expertise and their objective is to achieve long - term “ lock - in ” with their applications .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "As a result many organizations prefer to own their own vendor agnostic data warehouse enabling them to achieve independence from any software vendor and change applications more easily if it can help improve efficiency and or reduce cost .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Sometimes organizations end up using some type of hybrid approach of industry and / or vendor solutions combined with their own independently developed data warehouse solutions .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "In any case its important to have a data governance / quality strategy in place to ensure a single version of the truth and reduce complexity .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Where is the best place to start ?",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Typically organizations begin with an initial health check and / or assessment to determine their available data and resources to support a data warehouse initiative .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "As a result they can focus on the highest priority areas with highest available quality data to achieve an immediate impact .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "This is important to help reduce cost and risk of data warehouse .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Typically this also includes meeting with business executives to understand the areas of highest priority for the organization in order to align with business objectives for revenue growth operational efficiency financial stability etc .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Once this is in place typically a first phase data warehouse will focus on a specific subject area ( i.e. finance quality sales etc. ) together with a strategy to extend this platform for future phases .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "This strategy is much better than a big bang approach since it reduces initial timeframes and risk and allows for iteration along the way .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "What makes your offering unique at Integratus ?",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    35,
                    45,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Here at Integratus we bring a “ best of both worlds ” approach to our customers .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    8,
                    18,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Often vendors will tout their specific solution as optimal for all clients however we do not believe a one size fits all works for clients with unique competitive advantages .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Where there are gaps in available vendor solutions we have developed and deployed prebuilt data mart solutions for applications such as SAP and SuccessFactors .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "This enables our customers to take advantage of our development work and learnings from past implementations and achieve quick wins within as few as four weeks rather than waiting several months or years for a Phase 1 Data Warehouse .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "In addition our prebuilt data marts are not Band - Aid solutions they are extensible to integrate with many other vendor data warehouse solutions ( such as Epic Cogito or the RapidDecision EDW ) or they can be extended for an organizations overall independent vendor agnostic strategy .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "In addition we provide experts with 15 or more years ’ experience leading and delivering data warehouse strategies to very large complex organizations .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Many of our consultants operate in a key advisory capacity to CIO \"s\" with large institutions across the US .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    105,
                    107,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Our combination of management consulting leadership together with hands on development expertise ensure clients are able to fully achieve the “ best of both worlds ” in big picture strategy together with hands on tactical wins .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "By putting a strategy in place to leverage their existing technology investments and achieve quick wins we can help to virtually eliminate risk for clients in achieving their DW objectives .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "How can organizations learn more about Integratus ?",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    39,
                    49,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "We will be featured on an upcoming webcast discussing best practices integrating data from cloud applications ( such as SuccessFactors ) together with on - premise data sources ( such as SAP ) into a central vendor agnostic Data Warehouse .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Our special guest speaker is JP Godette one of the first 50 employees of Business Objects ( BI market - share leading toolset ) discussing best practices and lessons learned over the past 2 years DW .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    29,
                    39,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    73,
                    89,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "JP worked fro many of largest enterprise org ’s across the US on their data strategy and we ’re so happy to have him join .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    2,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    59,
                    61,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Also featuring Sal Hernandez found of Integratus over 15 years cross-industry experience with org ’s across the US .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    15,
                    28,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    38,
                    48,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    112,
                    114,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "We highly recommend folks check out our webcast Aug 19th and we ’ll be recording so if the time does n’t work you can reach out to us for a few copy of the recording .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "You can also reach us toll - free at 1 - 888 or by email ron.lehman@integratussolutions.com",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "For more information on the approaching webinar hosted by Integratus Solutions please visit .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    58,
                    78,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "About INTEGRATUS SOLUTIONS",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    6,
                    26,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Integratus is a boutique - consulting firm specializing in pre-built Business Intelligence ( BI ) and Data Warehouse ( DW ) solutions using the market - share leading SAP BusinessObjects software .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    10,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    167,
                    170,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "They employ a team of senior BI -DW consultants each typically with over 15 years of cross-industry experience .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    29,
                    35,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Integratus consultants have the combined experience of 100’s of successful BI - DW implementations across North America .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    10,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    106,
                    119,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "About PRBuzz.com PRBuzz.com is a press release distribution service that distributes press releases to online news sites and blogs to help customers with search engine optimization and create buzz about their web site , news or business .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    6,
                    27,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Overnight Finance : Clinton breaks with Obama on trade By Kevin Cirilli - 10/07/15 07:33 PM",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    20,
                    27,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    40,
                    45,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    58,
                    71,
                    "PER"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "EDT TOMORROW STARTS TONIGHT : HILLARY CLINTON TURNS SHARPLY TO THE LEFT .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    30,
                    45,
                    "PER"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Talk about a dramatic change of events .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "In two major moves sure to appease the liberal Elizabeth Warren - wing of the Democratic Party , Democratic presidential frontrunner Hillary Clinton opposed President Obama \"s\" trade policy program and got into the wonky weeds in defending Warren \"s\" Consumer Financial Protection Bureau ( CFPB )... in one day ...",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    47,
                    63,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    78,
                    94,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    133,
                    148,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    167,
                    172,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    240,
                    246,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    251,
                    287,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    290,
                    294,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "ADVERTISEMENT 1 . ) CLINTON BREAKS WITH OBAMA ON TRADE , via Vicki Needham and Amie Parnes : Hillary Clinton announced her opposition Wednesday to the Pacific Rim trade deal , breaking with President Obama in another move to the left for her presidential campaign ...",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    20,
                    27,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    40,
                    45,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    61,
                    74,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    79,
                    90,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    93,
                    108,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    200,
                    205,
                    "PER"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "\" What I know about it , as of today I \"m\" not in favor of what I \"ve\" learned about it , \" Clinton said in the interview with PBS .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    92,
                    99,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    127,
                    130,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "In a statement , she elaborated , saying that based on what she knew about the TPP , it failed to meet the \" high bar \" of creating good jobs , raising wages and advancing national security .",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "She also sought to explain why she was opposing a trade deal she appeared to back while serving as Obama \"s\" secretary of State .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    99,
                    104,
                    "PER"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Story : http://bit.ly/1L7fhny",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "-- CLINTON ON DEFENSE : \" I still believe in the goal of a strong and fair trade agreement in the Pacific as part of a broader strategy both at home and abroad , just as I did when I was Secretary of State .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    3,
                    10,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    98,
                    105,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "I appreciate the hard work that President Obama and his team put into this process and recognize the strides they made .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    42,
                    47,
                    "PER"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "But the bar here is very high and , based on what I have seen , I do \"nt\" believe this agreement has met it . \"",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "-- SANDERS TO CLINTON : \"\" FINALLY \".\"",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    3,
                    10,
                    "PER"
                ],
                [
                    14,
                    21,
                    "PER"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The self - described socialist from Vermont came out swinging in an email to supporters : \" As someone who voted against the North American Free Trade Agreement , the Central American Free Trade Agreement and Permanent Normal Trade Relations with China and who has helped lead the effort against the Trans - Pacific Partnership , I am glad that Secretary Clinton has now come on board .",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    36,
                    43,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    247,
                    252,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    355,
                    362,
